Ekaterine Mitagvaria



Summary

After working in different fields for over 9 years and seeking something special, I have recently found my passion in web development. Since October 2021 I have a career break in order to become a web developer. I am highly motivated to put all my time and effort into this field.

Education

High School N 154

Tbilisi, Georgia 2000-2012

Technical Expertise

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Tailwind
- Vanilla JavaScript ES6+
- · React.is
- RESTful API

- Responsive web design
- Github
- Git
- Visual Studio Code
- Figma

Skills

- Team player
- · Attentive to details
- Flexible
- Time management

- Visual thinker
- Adaptable
- Creative
- Self-learner

Professional Experience

Head of Department - Social Boost

Jan 2021 - Oct 2021

- Ensuring the team conducts bespoke campaigns based on clients' requirements to ensure client satisfaction.
- Ensure all company marketing practices are followed by the team correctly.
- Create, develop and test new growth strategies to improve results for company clients.
- Ensuring that retention rate targets are met by the team.
- Managing training syllabus for new recruits & holding training personally.
- Ensure the team acknowledges and acts to resolve all client complaints.
- Report team performance each week to the company Director.
- Keep written records of individual team member performance and record errors.
- Hold regular meetings and performance reviews with team leaders.

Team Lead - Social Boost

- Leading a team of Instagram Growth Specialists in growing Instagram Accounts organically for businesses and influencers.
- Working closely with the Client Success Management team to ensure all client's requirements are met.
- Reporting performance to management.
- Overseeing Organic Instagram growth campaigns.
- Ensuring the highest levels of quality across the team.

Instagram Growth Specialist - Social Boost

Jul 2020 - Sep 2020

- Hand-growing Instagram accounts manually via the Instagram app.
- Interacting with people to generate highly engaged niche audiences.
- Researching targets to ensure the highest quality Instagram growth is achieved.
- Organic Instagram growth techniques.
- Hashtag and competitor account research.
- · Audience and engagement building.
- · Quality control.

Sales Specialist Be-Canadian Immigration Agency

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020

- Reaching out to customers interested in immigration to Canada via phone calls (warm calls).
- Offering services using solid arguments and providing information on how immigration works.
- Maintaining positive business/customer relationships.
- Achieving monthly sales targets.
- Providing management with reports of daily activity using the CRM system.
- Writing custom e-mails to customers.
- Using follow-up/callback strategies.
- I also helped with hiring new people and providing them with training.

Chief Executive Officer - Catrisa (Self-employed)

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020

Online lingerie store start-up catrisa.ge. I was managing all the aspects of the
company on my own. Sales were done online/locally only. My first business
failed and the biggest reason was Covid-19 as I was unable to fulfill the orders
and refill the stock. Received a lot of experience in how retail business works
and improved my skills with customer support, web development, local SEO as
well as content and social media management.